hydranetwork.com 2011-10-12

# Privacy Policy | Adknowledge Affiliate

### Privacy Policy

We'll only use your info to serve the purpose for which you submitted it. And we definitely won't trade or sell it to anyone else.

That's the gist of our Privacy Policy in plain English. But if you can read legalese and you're so inclined, our full Privacy Policy is detailed below.

The policy was adopted, effective  
 **April 20, 2010**.

#### Information Collection and Use

##### Information Collection

Adknowledge is the sole owner of the information collected on our Publisher Solutions Network. Adknowledge Affiliate collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

##### Applications and Contact Forms

We request information from users on our affiliate applications as well as on our contact forms. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and other information) and, if applying to be an affiliate on Adknowledge Publisher Solutions, financial information as well (such as bank account information and payment preferences). This information is used to process your request. If we have difficulty processing your request, the information you provide may be used to contact you.

#### Information Use

##### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. We do not sell any personally identifiable information to third parties. 

##### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to keep track of a user's application when they move through our site. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. Cookies are required to submit your request to Adknowledge Publisher Solutions. We also use persistent cookies to track advertising activity. See <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie> for more information.

##### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

##### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are tied to users' personally identifiable information to allow us to keep track of the orders of users that have entered our site via third-party advertising.

In addition, we use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section.

#### Communications from the Site

##### Updates, Important Notices and Special Offers

We send all new customers a welcoming email to verify their password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on campaigns, products, services, and special deals, as well as important notices. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

##### Client Services

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts we reply via email, telephone, or instant message, in accordance with the users' wishes whenever possible.

##### Sharing

_Legal Disclaimer_ Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us. We do not sell any personally identifiable information to third parties.

##### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. However, we do store aggregate data so that we provide outside sources with general traffic statistics from our website (for example, we may use aggregate information in a press release that states "traffic at Adknowledge Publisher Solutions increased 40% this week.")

##### Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site by changing their profile preferences. Every user will receive an email confirmation of their username and password as well as instructions for how to login to their account. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by emailing us at [affiliate-unsubscribe@adknowledge.com](mailto:affiliate-unsubscribe@adknowledge.com). We also offer an opt-out mechanism on the user profile page or the user may contact us at **10940 Wilshire Blvd., Suite 1100, Los Angeles, CA, 90024, Attention: Unsubscribe** to opt-out.

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

##### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

##### Security

This Web site takes every reasonable precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as bank account information and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption. While on a secure page, such as our application form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer>.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also take measures to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or an account representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure Class-A environment, behind a locked cage in a locked facility that employs biometric security measures to restrict access physical access.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [affiliate-support@adknowledge.com](mailto:affiliate-support@adknowledge.com).

##### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support at [affiliate-support@adknowledge.com](mailto:affiliate-support@adknowledge.com). However, we may be required to maintain certain personally identifiable information in order to comply with applicable laws, in which case, your personally identifiable information will be secured and maintained until such time as we are no longer required to keep it.

##### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner.

##### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

**URL:** [http://www.adknowledge.com/publisher/affiliate/cpa](http://www.adknowledge.com/publisher/affiliate)

**Email:** [affiliate-support@adknowledge.com](mailto:affiliate-support@adknowledge.com)

**Postal Address:**  
Adknowledge Affiliate, Inc.  
10940 Wilshire Blvd, Suite 1100  
Los Angeles, California 90024
